(Howard:)How about a hug for Howie?
(Penny:)Sure. Raj, hug Howard.
[SHELDON SIGHS]
(Leonard:)Something you'd like to share?
A tale of woe perhaps?
(Gablehouser:)Fifteen years old.
Dennis Kim is 15 years old
and he's already correcting my work.
(Sheldon:)Today, I went from being
Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart to...
(Sheldon:)You know, that other guy.
(Howard:)Antonio Salieri?
(Sheldon:)Oh, God,
now even you're smarter than me.
You know, you don't have so many friends
that you can afford to start insulting them.
(Leonard:)Just eat, Sheldon. You'll feel better.
Why waste food?
(Sheldon:)When a cow goes dry,
they don't keep feeding it...
(Sheldon:)...they just take her out
and shoot her between the eyes.
(Penny:)I'm confused.
Did Sheldon stop giving milk?
(Leonard:)You can't let this kid get to you.
You knew that someday, someone would
come along who's younger and smarter.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but I assumed
I would've been dead hundreds of years.